phonezoo.com 2019-01-23

# 

Phonezoo.com Privacy Policy - Phonezoo understands that privacy is extremely important to you and is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information.

This Privacy Policy explains how Phonezoo.com (“Phonezoo") collects and uses personally identifiable information about visitors to the site and users of the service.    By visiting the Phonezoo site or using its services, you are accepting the practices outline in this Privacy Policy. This policy does not apply to the practices of   third    parties that Phonezoo does not own or control, or to individuals that Phonezoo does not employ or manage.   Phonezoo collects    non-personally   identifiable information when you visit our website (www.phonezoo.com).  This data includes your IP address, the IP address and URL of the Website that sent you to the Phonezoo main page, browser cookie and browser type.     This data is automatically recorded in our server logs and is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the Phonezoo website  and  services. When you use Phonezoo services and register for Phonezoo, we collect additional information such as your name, mobile phone number, mobile   phone device information and network carrier information. We also collect any optional information you choose to enter like email address,    location information (such as address,  zip  code,    and country), gender and age.When you connect to the Phonezoo services on your mobile device, if your mobile phone service provider uniquely identifies the device, Phonezoo will  receive  this  information.  Phonezoo may use your unique mobile device identification  information to   offer you   extended services and/or functionality. Some mobile phone  service  providers  are required  to operate a system  that  will  record the physical location of devices that use their service.

Depending on the mobile phone service provider,  Phonezoo may  automatically  receive  this  information. When  you  visit  the  Phonezoo  site,  we  may  send  one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser.   Phonezoo uses both session cookies - cookies that expire after you close your browser - and persistent cookies - cookies that can be used by your browser  on  subsequent  visits  to  the  site.  Some  of  our  business  partners  may  use cookies on our website (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.  The "help"  portion of  the toolbar  on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We strongly recommend that you  leave the  cookies  activated,  however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of Phonezoo's most  attractive features.  Phonezoo members can invite friends to join the service and preview content by  sending  invitation  emails  via  our  automated  invitation  system.  Phonezoo  stores  the email addresses that members provide so that the respondents may be added as Friends of the member sending the invitations, and also to send reminders of the invitations.  Phonezoo  does  not  sell  these email addresses or use them to send any other communication  besides  invitations,  invitation  reminders  (up to three (3) per email address).  We  will not sell, rent or otherwise distribute personal information to third parties without your  consent,  except  in  instances  described  below.  How Phonezoo uses your personal information Phonezoo uses your personal information to operate, maintain and provide  you  with  the features and functionality of the Phonezoo site and services.Phonezoo uses your mobile phone number to deliver the mobile content you create and other content you request.  Phonezoo  will  not  use  your  mobile  phone number to call you or send commercial or marketing messages. Additionally, Phonezoo will not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to  send  commercial  or  marketing messages without your consent except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or subsequently opt-out. We may,  however,  use  your  email  address  without  further  consent    for     non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Phonezoo service changes or for customer service purposes). 

Phonezoo uses personally identifiable and certain non-personally identifiable information so that:

You will not have to re-enter information during your visit or the next time you visit the Phonezoo site We can improve the quality and design of our website and services and to create new features and functionality We can monitor the effectiveness of our marketing  campaigns  We can monitor  aggregate  metrics  such  as  total  number  of  visitors,  pages viewed, etc. Any  personal  information  or  content that you voluntarily disclose online (on the Phonezoo site,  in  our  discussion,  rating  and  chat  areas,  within  your  public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly  available  and  can  be  collected  and  used  by  others.  Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other users when you upload contents or  send  messages from the Phonezoo site. Others  can  contact  you as a result  of  messages  you  send.  Any  text,  audio,  image  or  other  content  posted  at  the  direction  of  users  onto the Phonezoo site becomes published content and is not considered  personally  identifiable  information  for  the  purposes  of  this  Privacy  Policy.  In addition,  Phonezoo  may  use  comments  posted  in  public  areas  about the Phonezoo  site  o r services for editorial purposes or in promotional, advertising or marketing materials. Users who submit such comments in these public  places  on  the  site  grant   a non-exclusive, perpetual, irrevocable, transferable, royalty-free license to Phonezoo to transmit, publicly display, publicly perform, reproduce, edit, translate and  reformat  and  otherwise  use  such  public  information.

We  use  third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website.These companies may use information (not  including  your  name,  address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.  Google's  use  of  the  DART  cookie  enables  it  to serve ads to our  users  based  on  their  visit  to  this  sites  and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the  DART  cookie  by  visiting  the  Google.com. Information Sharing and Disclosure Phonezoo  will not sell,  rent  or  share  your  personal  information  with  anyone  unless  you have given us permission to share such information except in cases where we believe that disclosure is necessary to:(1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by Phonezoo,  whether  or  not  a  response   is required by applicable law; 

(2) to enforce the Phonezoo Terms of Use or to protect our rights; or

(3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service.

Phonezoo reserves the right to transfer personal information upon a transfer or sale to another entity of all or  substantially all  of  Phonezoo's  stock or assets.  For more information see the "Changes to Our Privacy Policy" section below.Security of Your Personal Information Your Phonezoo account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to work to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging  off  once you have finished using a shared  computer. We use industry-standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL)  software  to  protect  the  security  of  your  personal  information  during  transmission, which encrypts  all  of the  information  you  input.  Only  Phonezoo  employees  who  need  personal  information  to  perform  a  specific  job  ( for  example,  a  customer   service representative) are granted access to it. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices. Your ability to Edit  your  Account  Information  and Preferences.You may edit or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by  logging  into  your   account and accessing your My Zoo page. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from Phonezoo.  Please  note  that  content  uploaded  by  Users  to Phonezoo cannot be removed. You may request deletion of your Phonezoo account by accessing your MyZoo page. Please note that some information may remain in our  records  after  deletion of your account. For your privacy and security,  we  request  a  unique  password  to  verify  your identity before granting you profile access in order to make corrections or changes. International  Users  Phonezoo  site  is  hosted  in  the  United  States  and  is  intended  for  and  directed  to users in the United States.If you are a user accessing the Phonezoo site from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal  data collection,  use,  and  disclosure,  that  differ  from United States laws,  please  be advised that  through  your  continued use of the Phonezoo site, which is governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to  the  United State s and you  expressly  consent to that transfer. 

Links to other sites As part of the Phonezoo service, we may provide links to other websites and products. If you choose to visit a third party website or use its products or services, please be aware that the third party's privacy policy, not this Privacy Policy, will be in effect. Please review the  privacy  policies  of  these  sites  in  order  to  understand  their  privacy  policies  and  data  collection  practices. Phonezoo is  not  responsible  for  the  privacy  or  security  practices  or  the  content  of  these  websites.  Children under age 13 Phonezoo understands the importance of protecting the privacy of  children  under  13  years  of  age.  Therefore,  Phonezoo  does  not knowingly  collect  or  maintain  personally  identifiable  information  or  non-personally-identifiable  information  from  persons  under  13 years of age.  Further,  no  part of our website or service is directed to persons under 13.  If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the Phonezoo site or services at any time or in any manner. Changes to our Privacy Policy From time to time,  Phonezoo may make changes to this Privacy Policy at its sole discretion. If we make changes, we will post them on our site. Please revisit this page to stay informed of the  current policy and any changes. Any changes will be reflected in the "effective date" below. Use of information  we  collect  now  is  subject  to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. 

Conditions of Use.If you decide to visit the Phonezoo site or use the Phonezoo services, your visit and/or use  and  any  possible  dispute  over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.  Questions about our Privacy Policy .If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at: support@phonezoo.com. Effective date: 2015
